









# CONTACTS



Russia, Cheboksary



+7 999 199 05 90



ru9art@gmail.com



<u>Portfolio</u>

### **PROFILE**

Front-End developer with experience in creating SPA using React, Apollo GraphQL/Redux, TypeScript as the main stack, and I want to develop in this direction. Now I am improving my skills in this direction and expanding them with new technologies. I'm studying Node.js, because my next focus is to become a Full-Stack Developer. I spend my free time studying English and technical documentation.

Ready to consider project work and full-time employment.

# **SKILLS**

- GraphQL, Apollo, TypeORM
- React, Express, PostgreSQL
- Redux & Toolkit, Thunk, Saga
- Formik, React Native, Expo
- Recoil, TypeScript, JavaScript
- RestAPI, Axios, WebSocket
- Styled Component, SCSS
- TDD, Unit Tests, Storybook
- Material UI, Ant Design
- Git, Jira, Heroku, AGILE, SCRUM

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English A1
- Russian Native

# **VLADISLAV** MUZYKA

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

cmdF5 | May 2021 - Present 2021 - 9 months

- Implemented new features on the Back-End, such as:
  - Used TypeORM to create relationships between tables and entity classes to access and update information in the database.
  - Created GraphQL queries and mutations to interact with PostgreSQL database.
  - Implementing mailing using Express and Nodemailer
  - Login implementation using JWT token
- As for the Front-End:
  - CRUD operations using Apollo GraphQL, updating cache after
  - Using UI library Mui (Material UI) and integration with Formik library.

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER

FREELANCE / TEAM WORK | Apr 2021 - Jun 2021 - 2 months

- Project architectural solutions (layering UI, BLL, DAL)
- Implementation of new features such as:
  - RESTful (Registration / loginization / pagination etc.)
  - Proper BLL state management with Redux, Thunk etc.
  - During the development process, I wrote tests for the reducer (TDD) using Jest.
  - Translated the application to the Redux Toolkit to set a clear and understandable flow and simplify debugging in the future.
  - o TDD with Jest, Storybook, Postman
  - Performance enhancement (memo, useMemo, useCallback, lazy loading, Suspense etc.)
  - Migration to Typescript

#### My Hobby

2012 - 2018

- Development of websites based on CMS WordPress, DLE, Joomla and many others.
- Development of a game server on a linux VPS/VDS system
- Developing simple plugins in Pawn

## **EDUCATION HISTORY**

#### **IT-INCUBATOR**

Front-End Developer

(React, Redux, TypeScript) | 2021

• Work with React, Redux, TypeScript, Promise, REST API, GIT, immutable.js, Heroku, Material UI, Ant Design, StoryBook, TDD

# HTML-ACADEMY & Cheb electromechanical college

Front-End | Aug 2020 - Jan 2021

Basic course in HTML5. CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript, React, Vue, PHP